const QUESTIONS = [

    {
      "id": 1,
      "category": "CSS",
      "value": "$200",
      "question": "Which property is used to change the font color of an element",
      "answer": "color"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "category": "CSS",
      "value": "$400",
      "question": "Which property is used to change the font size of an element”",
      "answer": "font-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "category": "CSS",
      "value": "$600",
      "question": "The outermost component of the CSS “box-method",
      "answer": "margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "category": "CSS",
      "value": "$800",
      "question": "If no positioning is set in a CSS element, what is the default positioning",
      "answer": "static"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "category": "CSS",
      "value": "$1000",
      "question": "What is the primary difference between grid and flexbox",
      "answer": "grid is 2 dimensional & flexbox is 1 dimensional"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "category": "HTML",
      "value": "$200",
      "question": "The elements that need to be put inside of a form are input, button and",
      "answer": "label"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "category": "HTML",
      "value": "$400",
      "question": "What tag defines a cell in a table",
      "answer": "<td></td>"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "category": "HTML",
      "value": "$600",
      "question": "What element creates a form",
      "answer": "<form></form>"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "category": "HTML",
      "value": "$800",
      "question": "The <img> requires a closing </img> to be valid",
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "category": "HTML",
      "value": "$1000",
      "question": "Which best describes the <canvas> element",
      "answer": "container for graphics"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "category": "JavaScript",
      "value": "$200",
      "question": "Everything in JavaScript is an object",
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "category": "JavaScript",
      "value": "$400",
      "question": "Local storage data is stored in",
      "answer": "file system"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "category": "JavaScript",
      "value": "$600",
      "question": "JavaScript is a case-sensitive language",
      "answer": "true"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "category": "JavaScript",
      "value": "$800",
      "question": "A function __________ loads before any code is executed",
      "answer": "declaration"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "category": "JavaScript",
      "value": "$1000",
      "question": "A function ______ loads only when the interpreter reaches that line of code",
      "answer": "expression"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "category": "Git",
      "value": "$200",
      "question": "Git automatically adds new files to the repository",
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "category": "Git",
      "value": "$400",
      "question": "What command is used to create to a new branch called name",
      "answer": "git checkout -b name"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "category": "Git",
      "value": "$600",
      "question": "The following command will add all changes to be staged for commit",
      "answer": "git add ."
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "category": "Git",
      "value": "$800",
      "question": "What are the three steps to get changes from the local machine to github",
      "answer": "add commit push"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "category": "Git",
      "value": "$1000",
      "question": "To download a Git repository named 'repo' on your local machine for the first time which Git command would you use",
      "answer": "git clone https:github.com/repo"
    }
  
  ];
  